hotlyrics.net 2018-06-30

# HostSG Legal Agreement

When you register for a HostSG account or reseller program, HostSG obtains contact information, such as your name, email and postal address, and phone number, as well as payment information, such as your credit card number. When you use HostSG's service, our systems record information about your session, such as the dates and times of use, and the specific Internet address assigned to you. To do this we may use standard web server log files as well as session or persistent based cookies. HostSG also tracks requests you make for information on HostSG's products and services, and responses you provide to HostSG surveys. Finally, HostSG keeps records of your payment history and communications you have with HostSG's support team. Except in extraordinary circumstances (when we receive a court order, to protect the company's rights or property, or in emergencies where someone's safety is at risk), HostSG does not keep track of what sites you visit when you are using the service as an identifiable individual.

**What Information Does HostSG Gather?**

When you register for a HostSG account, HostSG obtains contact information, such as your name, address, and phone number, as well as payment information, such as your credit card number. When you use HostSG's service, our systems record information about your session, such as the dates and times of use, and the specific Internet address assigned to you. HostSG also tracks requests you make for information on HostSG's products and services, and responses you provide to HostSG surveys. Finally, HostSG keeps records of your payment history and communications you have with HostSG's support team. Except in extraordinary circumstances (when we receive a court order, to protect the company's rights or property, or in emergencies where someone's safety is at risk), HostSG does not keep track of what sites you visit when you are using the service.

**What Does HostSG Do With This Information?**

HostSG uses the information it gathers in order to provide you with the best online experience possible. As you might expect, contact information is used to contact you concerning your account and our company. Payment information is used to validate your identity and to bill you for the services and products you order. Information on your online sessions is used to allocate system resources and to ensure compliance with HostSG's Service Level Agreements (SLAs). Information on your communications with HostSG's support team is used to address the issues raised by your communications. In addition, HostSG regularly sends out mailings regarding the operation of its service and other goods and services that it believes may be of interest to you. You may request that HostSG not send you mailings relating to other goods and services at the URLs listed in this section or send an e-mail to support@HostSG.com. HostSG reserves the right, however, to send bulletins and other important information regarding the service at its discretion.

**Does HostSG Share Subscriber Information With Third Parties?**

HostSG will not share or disclose information regarding its subscribers except (i) when we receive legal process such as a court order or are required to disclose the information by law ; (ii) when reasonably necessary to protect the company's rights or property; (iii) in emergencies where someone's safety is at risk; (iv) or as required for domain name registration (e.g.whoislookup).

You should be aware, however, that any information that you disclose in a public space such as a bulletin board, or personal Web site, HostSG's DNR domain registration is freely available to anyone else visiting that space. HostSG cannot safeguard any personally identifiable information you disclose in these locations, nor can it ensure that information you voluntarily supply to third parties remains private. Please review the privacy policies of third party sites you frequent to ensure that your privacy preferences are respected.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security

**How Can I Correct or Update the Information?**

You may correct that information by updating us with your new information to support@HostSG.com. Please keep in mind that under HostSG's Service Level Agreements (SLAs), subscribers are required to provide HostSG with current contact and billing information. HostSG may require a copy of a government issued form of identification before disclosing billing information or before making changes to the billing or contact information on an account. 

**What Happens to the Information if I Leave HostSG?**  
If you ever leave HostSG, HostSG will normally delete your personally identifiable account information twelve months after the account is cancelled, unless we are under a legal obligation to retain it. We preserve account information for this short period of time in the event you wish to reactivate your account and retain your previous e-mail address. However, in the event of any accounting irregularities, HostSG reserves the right to retain your contact and billing information as necessary to resolve the matter. 

**Changes to This Policy and Questions About Privacy**

HostSG reserves the right to make changes to this policy. Minor changes will become effective immediately upon posting them to this privacy statement. However, those changes that are material will become effective 30 days after notice of them is posted here, on the site or emailed or emailed with an appropriate effective time frame. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please open a ticket at [http://my.hostsg.com ](http://my.hostsg.com/)
